Narrator: 1
Satnav: After 100 metres, turn right. Turn right.
Lisa: Don’t turn left! Turn right!
Mel: It’s left, I’m sure.
Lisa: No, it isn’t.
Mel: Yes, it is!
Lisa: No, it isn’t! This is wrong!
Narrator: 2
Lisa: I’m thirsty. Where’s the water?
Mel: Sorry, it’s empty.
Lisa: Empty?
Mel: Yes, empty. I’m hungry. And Alfie’s hungry. Let’s stop at a café.
Lisa: OK, good idea.
Narrator: 3
Mel: Brr…
Lisa: What’s the matter?
Mel: I’m cold. Can you close your window?
Lisa: I’m not cold! I’m hot!
Mel: Well, I’m cold. And Alfie’s cold.
Lisa: OK.
Mel: And please don’t drive fast! It’s really dangerous.
Lisa: It’s fine. Don’t worry!
Mel: Be careful!
Narrator: 4
Lisa: It’s late. Let’s look for a hotel.
Mel: Oh, let’s not stop now.
Lisa: I’m tired and it’s dark. And Alfie’s tired, too.
Mel: OK, OK. Look for a hotel near here.
Lisa: The Highland Hotel’s 20 miles from here.
Mel: Fine, no problem. Let’s go there.